

Hoang Do

Web developer

About Me

Hello! I'm Hoang Do. I am passionate about web development. I am a skilled Back-end Developer, familiar with web frameworks such as PHP-Laravel or Java-Spring. I'm also experienced with Front-end framework like React, Angular or VueJS.

DOB 02/01/1994

Email hoangdo.2194@gmail.com

Phone +84 35 537 4643

Address 751 Bach Dang, Hai Ba Trung, Ha Noi, Viet Nam

Professional Skills

PHP - Laravel

Java - Spring

HTML

CSS	
JavaScript	
ReactJS	
Angular	
VueJS	

Work Experience

Web developer at TopCV

January, 2021 - Present

Maintain, design systems and databases, development projects and features for the company's productions, focus to the TopCV system and the internal operating systems. Training for another employees, and sometimes take the PM's role for some small projects.

Web Developer at Amit Group

September, 2018 - January, 2021

Design systems, databases base on customer's requirements, develop and maintain the backend and frontend (admin sites) for most of the projects. I am also responsible for develop and deploy the products in all of its life cycle.

Education

Bachelor in Software Engineering from FPT University

2021 - Present

Learn to become true software engineering, I am always know that I must learn more and never stop if I want to go further, and I also want to take the certificates from the university.

Higher diploma in software engineering from FPT Aptech

2017 - 2019

Learned to become a Developer, rounded my expects, and take a job, nothing more about it.

Bachelor in Nuclear Engineering from HUST

2012 - 2014

I've learned at HUST, but then I left after 2 years because the major is not my favorite one.

Projects

React hook guard the open source

2021

A routing and guarding library for reactjs, base on react-router-dom 5. I made it after 3 months work with react and the original react-router-dom library. It's help me and my peers to easier control the routing, multiple layouts and authentication, authorization features of react app.

tindohanghieu.com

2019

A web system provide for the brands fans, can trade, or buy the popular brands items.

- Main functions: Social, Chat, Live Stream.
- Responsibilities: Design systems, Backend developer, frontend (admin site) developer, compose with frontend (customer site), deployment.
- Language Framework: PHP (Laravel), Mysql, NodeJs (NestJs Framework), Angular.
- Coverage: Backend ~ 70% Frontend ~ 50% (Admin site).

Hoang Cong Car

2018 - 2019

Hoang Cong is a domestic privatized transportation company that runs the vehicles from Hanoi to Quang Ninh and vice versa. Customer can call to operators or book ticket by themselves on the website.

- Main functions: Place ticket, manage voyages, balances,...
- Responsibilities: Design systems, Backend developer, frontend (admin site) developer, deployment.

- Language Framework: PHP (Laravel), MySql, Angular, VueJs.
- Coverage: Backend ~ 90% Frontend ~ 80% (Admin site).

Various Projects from TopCV and Amit Group

2018 - present

I've developed and maintained various projects for TopCV and Amit Group. Such as the topcv.vn and its internal systems. Or other outsource products such as E-Caf by Pan United using Spring Boot - Java, or tangthuvien.vn,...
But because of the policies, or the products are not run anymore, so I can not show them here.

Contact

Address

751 Bach Dang, Hai Ba Trung, Ha Noi, Viet Nam

Phone

+084 35 537 4643

Email

hoangdo.2194@gmail.com

A

https://www.facebook.com/hoangdo.2194

(0)

https://www.instagram.com/hoangdo.2194

https://github.com/aaaahoang123